<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Web3 on ReFi Barcelona</title>
    <link>https://example.org/tags/web3/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Web3 on ReFi Barcelona</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/tags/web3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/projects/akasha_hub/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/projects/akasha_hub/</guid>
      <description>Summary: AKASHA Hub serves as a beacon in the intersection of technology, sustainability, and community-driven innovation. Established in 2017, it has been instrumental in fostering the growth of the web3 ecosystem and aligns closely with the regenerative finance movement.&#xA;Introduction AKASHA Hub, based in Barcelona, operates with the core mission of integrating web3 technologies to promote sustainability and positive social change. It traces its origins to the early days of the Ethereum Foundation, indicating a deep-rooted history in blockchain innovation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/projects/refi-barcelona/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/projects/refi-barcelona/</guid>
      <description>ReFi Barcelona Page under construction 🚧 👷 🏗️.Q</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/projects/refi-dao/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/projects/refi-dao/</guid>
      <description>ReFi DAO Our mission is focused on developing strategic services and public goods for the Regenerative Finance (ReFi) ecosystem including movement-wide sense-making, education, opportunity development, fundraising support, onboarding and empowerment through a blend of online platforms, multimedia, and community coordination.&#xA;Central to our work is incubating and supporting the development of ReFi Local Nodes across all major regions in the world. These local communities are pivotal in championing ReFi solutions on the ground and enacting a cosmo-local network for the regenerative economy.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
